rnel.net 2010-12-29

# Privacy Policy

RNELdotNET sets out this privacy policy to protect any information that you give on this website. 

When you visit this website RNELdotNET may collect personal data about you, either directly (where you are asked to provide the data) or indirectly. RNELdotNET will, however, only use these personal data in accordance with the purposes set forth in this Privacy Statement and is committed to safeguarding the personal information collected. This statement sets out the purposes of RNELdotNET's data processing in respect of this website, the use of cookies and how to affect your rights in respect of your personal data. 

Purposes of processing  
RNELdotNET collects and processes information about it's visitors to its website for the development of web statistics. The information you provide will be used to contact you when necessary, e.g. to notify you about functionality changes to the website and to present new website services that you may find helpful (provided you have not opted out to receive such services). 

Sensitive data  
RNELdotNET does not seek to collect sensitive personal data through this website. 

Cookies  
RNELdotNET may gather and analyse information regarding usage of this website, including domain name, the number of hits, the pages visited, previous/subsequent sites visited and length of user session. This information may be gathered by using a cookie. A cookie is a small text file placed on your hard drive by our web page server. You can choose whether or not to use a cookie by altering the settings of your browser. A cookie will make the use of this website faster and easier. 

Use of Images  
When you submitted your copyrighted image to this website RNELdotNET is committed to you that it won't use any of your image(s) commercially but for a sample preview only. 

Third party sites  
Please note that this Privacy Statement does not extend to third party sites linked from this website. Please check out their Privacy Statement. . 

How to Contact RNELdotNET  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement you can contact us at editor_AT_RNELdotNET 

Amendments  
RNELdotNET reserves the right to modify sections of this Privacy Statement at any time. Please check this statement from time to time for any changes.
